[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":28462,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":69225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":12703,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":81929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1783,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":83713,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":87856,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1416,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":89273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":11080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":100353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":920,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":101273,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3215,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":104488,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1400,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":105889,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6  or bigge r, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3056,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":108946,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":975,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":109922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3175,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":113098,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2- 0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1191,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":114290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":117538,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1048,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":118586,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to pe rform +< sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":122401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1895,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":124297,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3568,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":127866,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1055,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":128922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4287,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":133210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1016,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":134226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":12087,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":146314,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similar ly, 3 is  its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":31550,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":177866,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":9605,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":187473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1135,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":188609,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an e lement i s the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3384,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":191993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1063,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":193056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2456,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":195513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":" Correct!  The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1391,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":196905,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":199745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":991,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":200737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br  /> (Reme mber, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4520,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":205257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5838,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":211096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":10016,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":221113,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We h ave one  last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":75384,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":296498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can mak e every  other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":13997,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":310497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":2479,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":312977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":12792,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":325769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a g enerator  under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":11815,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":337585,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":24911,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":362497,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6 </sub> 4 , and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":12423,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":374921,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":18591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":393513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1023,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":394537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the nu mbers 0,  1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":13343,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":407881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4863,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":412745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1112,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":413857,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<su b>9</sub > 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":7872,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":421730,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4007,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":425737,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3311,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":429049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":436777,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3000,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":439778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4+1 = 5, which is under 9, so we leave the answer as is, which is 5","response_history":["4+1 = 5, which is under 9, so we leave the answer as is, which is 5"],"rt":31743,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":471521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4=12-9= 3. Becau se 8+4 is greater than 9, we take the sum and subtract 9 from it. 12-9=3 so the final answer is 3.","response_history":["8+4 ","8+4=12-9=3. Because 8+1","8+4=12-9=3. Because 8+4 is greater than 9, we take the sum,","8+4=12-9=3. Because 8+4 is greater than 9, we take the sum and subtract 9 from it. 12 - 9","8+4=12-9=3. Because 8+4 is greater than 9, we take the sum and subtract 9 from it. 12- 9","8+4=12-9=3. Because 8+4 is greater than 9, we take the sum and subtract 9 from it. 12-9= 3","8+4=12-9=3. Because 8+4 is greater than 9, we take the sum and subtract 9 from it. 12-9= ","8+4=12-9=3. Because 8+4 is greater than 9, we take the sum and subtract 9 from it. 12-9=3 so the final answer is 3."],"rt":35744,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":507265,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an identity under +9 because combining 0 with anything gives the same thing back.","response_history":["Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an under","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an unde","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an und","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an un","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an u","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an identity under +9 be cause co mbining 0 with anything gives the same result back.","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an identity under +9 because combining 0 with anything gives the same t back.","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an identity under +9 because combining 0 with anything gives the same th back.","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an identity under +9 because combining 0 with anything gives the same thi back.","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an identity under +9 because combining 0 with anything gives the same thin back.","Identity under +9 is any number that can be combined with the +9 operation that returns the same thing back. 0 is an identity under +9 because combining  0 with a nything gives the same thing back."],"rt":126504,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":633770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":63925,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":697698,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":3591,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":701290,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"To get the identity back, you need to fin d what c ombines with 3 to return 0 under the operation +9. Adding 6 to 3 = 9. After the +9 operation, the answer 0 is returned, therefore the inverse is 6.","response_history":["To get the identity back, you need to find what combines with 3 to return 0.","To get the identity back, you need to find what combines with 3 to return 0 under the operation +9. Adding 3","To get the identity back, you need to find what combines with 3 to return 0 under the operation +9. Adding 6 to 3 = 9. After the +9 operation, 0","To get the identity back, you need to find what combines with 3 to return 0 under the operation +9. Adding 6 to 3 = 9. After the +9 operation, the answer 0 is returned, therefore the inverse is 6."],"rt":52262,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":753553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7=0, 2+8=1, 2+9=2, 2+10=3, etc. ","response_history":["1","2 is a generater","2 is a generate","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number ","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7 =","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7 ","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7+9","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7+","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2 and 7 =","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2 and","2 is a generator und er +9 be cause it is possible to create every other number. 2 an","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2 a","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2 ","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7=0, 2+8=1, 2+9,","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7=0, 2+8=1, 2+9=2, 2+2","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7=0, 2+8=1, 2+9=2, 2+10=3,  ","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7=0, 2+8=1, 2+9=2, 2+10=3, et ","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7=0, 2+8=1, 2+9=2, 2+10=3, etc ","2 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to create every other number. 2+7=0, 2+8=1, 2+9=2, 2+10=3, etc. "],"rt":211209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":964763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to get all other numbers using the +9 operation.","response_history":["Should b","Should ","Should","Shoul","Shou","Sho","Sh","S","3 is a generatore","3 is a generator","3 is a generator under +9 because it is possible to get all other numbers using the +9 operation."],"rt":120269,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1085035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It is possible to get all the other numbers using the +9 operation, so 5 is a generator under +9.","response_history":["It is possible to get all the other  numbers  using the +9  ","It is possible to get all the other numbers using the +9 operation, so 4","It is possible to get all the other numbers using the +9 operation, so 5 is a generator under +9."],"rt":85877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1170914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It is possible to get all other numbers using the +9 operation, so 6 is a generator under +9","response_history":["It is possible to get all other numbers using the +9 operation, so 6 is a generator under +9"],"rt":138333,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1309250,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could b e 3, or  n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":12309,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1321562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +n ","response_history":["1 under +1","1 under +n = 0, so n-1 is the ","n-1 is the  ","n-1 is the f ","n-1 is the fo ","n-1 is the for ","n-1 is the form ","n-1 is the formu ","n-1 is the formul ","n-1 is the formula  ","n-1 is the formula f ","n-1 is the formula for t ","n-1 is the formula for th ","n-1 is the formula for the  ","n-1 is the formula for the i ","n-1 is the formula for the in ","n-1 is the formula for the inv ","n-1 is the formula for the i nver "," n-1 is the formula for the inverse  ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of  ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1 ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1u ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1  ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1 u ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1 und ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1 under  ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1 under + ","n-1 is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +n "],"rt":177200,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1498763,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and x was 1, 1+2=3, and under  the +3 o peration, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","response_history":["If for example, element","If for example, elemen","If for example, eleme","If for example, elem","If for example, ele","If for example, el","If for example, e","If for example, x under ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 3","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 3 for +3, we use 3 + ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of  for +3, we use 3 + ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 4 = ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 +  = ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 1 =  ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 1 = 4  ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 1  = 4 -  ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 1 = 4 - 3  ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 1 = 4 - 3 =  ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 1 = 4 - 3 = 1 ","If for example, +n is 3, and we want to find the inverse of 1 for +3, we use 3 + 1 = 4 - 3 = 1. ","I don't know the exact formula, but any","I don't know the exact formula, but an","I don't know the exact formula, but a","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n=3","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n=0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n 0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n t0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything  combine d with x+n to0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to 0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to m0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to ma0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make 0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make th0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the 0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the i0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the id0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, any thing co mbined with x+n to make the ide0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the iden0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the ident0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identi0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identif0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identify0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identif0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identi0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identit0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity0","I don't know the exact formula, but for X  under + n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse ","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+3","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and the ","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and the","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and th","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and t","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined  with x+n  to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and under the +36","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0 as the ","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, ","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation,","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything c ombined  with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example , 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example a, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and , 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse.  So, if  +n was +3 for example and X, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and X , 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and X wa, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and X was, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and X was ,  1+2=3,  and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and X was 1, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and  was 1, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse.","I don't know the exact formula, but for X under +n, anything combined with x+n to make the identity 0 would be the inverse. So, if +n was +3 for example and x was 1, 1+2=3, and under the +3 operation, we'd get 0, and 2 would be the inverse."],"rt":428878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1927644,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are genera tors? Ho w can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Uncertain as to how to answer this question without seeing whether the x can make all the elements.","response_history":["It seems that odd nubmer","It seems that odd nubme","It seems that odd nubm","It seems that odd nub","It seems that odd numbers work well as generators","Uncertain as to how to answer this question without seeing whether the element ","Uncertain as to how to answer this question without seeing whether the x can make all the elements."],"rt":292635,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2220282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"Tru e","response_history":["True"],"rt":6390,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2226675,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4151,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2230827,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":9199,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2240027,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Plea se expla in in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, 2 was not a generator, and is a divisor and multiple of 6. Seems to work.","response_history":["I do not know. ","I do not know.","I do not know for ceta","I do not know for cet","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example where +6","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of +6","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of t +6","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of th +6","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the  +6","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, x ","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, x","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, ","I do not know for c ertain,  but using the previous example of the +6 operator, 2 was not a generator of ","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, 2 was not a generator of","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, 2 was not a generator o","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, 2 was not a generator ","I do not know for certain, but using the previous example of the +6 operator, 2 was not a generator, and is a divisor and multiple of 6. Seems to work."],"rt":88207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2328236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":8661,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2336899,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Uncertain - if the element x is a generator, then x+nx is sometimes a generator but not always the case.","response_history":["I don't know how to answer this question.","Uncertain - if it ","Uncertain - if it","Uncertain - if i","Uncertain - if t","Uncertain - if the element x is a generator, then it should always ","Uncertain - if the element x is a generator, then x+nx is sometimes a generator but not all","Uncertain - if the element x is a generator, then x+nx is sometimes a generator but not always the case."],"rt":103575,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2440475,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":4357,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2444835,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":1494,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2446330,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":3080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2449411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3504,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2452916,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Statistics","response_history":["Statistics"],"rt":10470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2463387,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept  of modul ar arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6704,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2470092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2473868,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2478100,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2481147,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":2447,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2483595,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1928,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2485524,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2489476,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":3800,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2493276,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without penalty, let your participants know that it's okay if they cannot provide an explanation.","response_history":["Lea","Le","L","Forcing explanations when the participant may or may no t","Forcing explanations when the participant may or may no ","Forcing explanations when the participant may or may not know the answer is not","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may no","Let your participants know whether or  not they  HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may n","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasph","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers at the ","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the latter ","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the latter","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the latte","Let your participants know  whether  or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the latt","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't e","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without penta","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without pent","Let your  partici pants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without penalty, let your participants know that it's OKA","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without penalty, let your participants know that it's OK","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without penalty, let your  partici pants know that it's Oka","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without penalty, let your participants know that it's Ok","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections can be skipped without penalty, let your participants know that it's O","Let your participants know whether or not they HAVE to provide written explanations for things they may or may not be able to explain. I found myself grasping for answers in the later portions of the HIT because I wasn't able to explain things properly. If these sections  can be  skipped without penalty, let your participants know that it's okay if they cannot provide an explanation."],"rt":90880,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2584156,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]